Guide to the Boyce D. McDaniel papers, 1933-2002.
McDaniel, Boyce D. papers, 1933-2002
- Series XV. Binder Materials
  - Mori, Shigeki, Photoproduction of Hypercharge-Zero Resonant States from Hydrogen, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Sadoff, Ahren Joel, Photoproduction of K+ Mesons in Hydrogen at 1160 MEV, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Weil, John William, The Production of Protons from Carbon by Monoenergetic Gamma-Rays, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Gorman Stearns, Mary Beth, Nuclear Scattering of 17 MEV Gamma-Rays, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Stanton, Noel R., Photoproduction of K+ Mesons in Hydrogen at 1400 MEV, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Anderson, Robert L., Detection of Photoproduced K+ Mesons from Hydrogen Employing a Modulated Bremsstrahlung Beam, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 13)